<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Say Cheese</string>
    <string name="cheese_image">Cheese image</string>
    <string-array name="categhory">
        <item>Cheese List</item>
        <item>Cheese Manufacturing Companies</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--  Cheese types and infos  -->

    <string name="mazarella_title">Mazarella</string>
    <string name="parmesan_title">Parmesan</string>
    <string name="cheddar_title">Cheddaer</string>
    <string name="gouda">Gouda</string>
    <string name="swiss_cheese">Swiss cheese</string>
    <string name="emmentaler">Emmentaler</string>
    <string name="brie">Brie</string>
    <string name="camembert">Camembert</string>
    <string name="gruyere_cheese">Gruyère cheese</string>
    <string name="feta">Feta</string>
    <string name="monterey_jack">Monterey Jack</string>
    <string name="provolone">Provolone</string>
    <string name="edam">Edam</string>
    <string name="blue_cheese">Blue cheese</string>
    <string name="gorgonzola">Gorgonzola</string>
    <string name="roquefort">Roquefort</string>
    <string name="ricotta">Ricotta</string>
    <string name="cottage_cheese">Cottage cheese</string>
    <string name="mascarpone">Mascarpone</string>
    <string name="halloumi">Halloumi</string>

    <string name="mazarella_info">Mozzarella may be the most popular cheese of all. It’s a southern
        Italian dairy product traditionally made from buffalo milk. Fresh mozzarella is generally
        white, usually rolled into balls of different sizes – from perline, which is the smallest
        (0.03-ounce/1 gram) to ovoline (4 ounces/113 grams). But it can be found in even bigger
        sizes: half pound balls or pound logs. There also is low-moisture mozzarella, which is aged
        cheese, harder and with a buttery color.
        You can enjoy fresh mozzarella with a drizzle of olive oil, coarse salt, and pepper,
        because it has a slightly acidic or lactic taste, but not salty. You can make a simple
        Caprese salad or eat it with tomatoes in a sandwich. Keep in mind that the best pizzas
        are never without mozzarella!</string>
    <string name="parmesan_info">Parmesan, or Parmigiano-Reggiano, is considered to be among the
        top cheeses by cheese connoisseurs. It’s a hard, granular cheese with a strong, nutty,
        and bitter taste, and that’s the reason you should add a small quantity to your dishes.
        Parmesan is mostly grated over pasta, used in soups and risottos. It is also eaten as is,
        as a snack or in cheese sauces. You can make crusts with panko, eggs, and parmesan
        for coating chicken before frying it, sprinkle it over a casserole dish or a salad,
        or add it into salty muffins.</string>
    <string name="cheddar_info">Cheddar cheese is dry and crumbly in texture, with a deep, tangy,
        nutty flavor. The color varies from ivory to straw to deep yellow. Cheddar is used to
        top burgers, as well as in other types of sandwiches. You can use Cheddar over casseroles
        or grated, in cheese sauces such as the one for mac and cheese, or to make veggie pies
        or quiches.</string>
    <string name="gouda_info">One of the most popular cheeses worldwide, Gouda is a semi-hard to
        hard cow’s milk cheese from the Netherlands. When Gouda is aged the cheese changes its
        flavor and texture. Aged Gouda has a strong flavor, with a sharp yet sweet taste at the same time.
        Young Gouda can be melted, but aged cheese is best as is or grated in salads or over
        casseroles. If you eat it simple, have it with beer, orange or apple juice, flavored tea,
        red wine, or white wine.</string>
    <string name="swiss_cheese_info">Swiss cheese resembles Emmentaler cheese. It’s a pale yellow
        color, medium-hard cheese. Some types of Swiss cheese are riddled with holes known as ‘eyes’,
        except for the ones who don’t have ‘eyes’ and are known as ‘blind’. It’s one of the most
        popular cheeses in America.
        Its mild, sweet and nut-like flavor makes it suitable mostly for sandwiches – especially for
        Reuben sandwiches – but people usually add it to dishes like pies, frittatas, souffles, or
        omelets, melted on a steak, in cheese sauces or fondue.</string>
    <string name="emmentaler_info">Emmental or Emmentaler is what many people think of when they
        hear of ‘Swiss cheese’ because they’re quite similar. This cheese is mild, a little sweet,
        slightly nutty, and a bit spicy at the end. You can use it in many dishes, but especially
        when you make cordon bleu, fondue, grilled cheese, and casseroles.</string>
    <string name="brie_info">Brie is a soft cow’s milk cheese from north-eastern France, pale in
        color with a slight grayish tinge under a rind of white mold. This cheese has a nutty,
        fruity, grassy, and even mushroom-like flavor, similar to Camembert. Some people find it
        unpleasantly acidic, others think it’s pleasant, buttery, and a bit tangy.
        Brie and meat make a great combo, but you can also spread the cheese over a slice of
        baguette. You can also serve baked brie with honey and apples, as a sweet dish.</string>
    <string name="camembert_info">Brie and Camembert look and taste alike, and they’re often
        served in similar ways. Yet there are subtle differences: Camembert has a deeper and
        more intense flavor. You can make baked Camembert and serve it with cheese crackers,
        toasted ciabatta slices, or garlic bread. You can also eat Brie and Camembert as is,
        with grapes and red wine.</string>
    <string name="gruyere_cheese_info">Gruyère is a hard cheese, yellow in color, sweet but
        slightly salty, with a flavor that varies depending on its age. Gruyère cheese is
        generally known as one of the finest cheeses for baking because it’s great for melting.
        Traditionally, you use it to make cheese sauce. You can also add it to fondue. It’s a fine
        table cheese. It can be used grated in salads and pasta. A French onion soup isn’t complete
        without it.</string>
    <string name="feta_info">Feta is a Greek cheese made with sheep and goat milk. It’s a white
        brined cheese, salty, tangy, and moist, with a texture that can go from crumbly to
        moderately creamy. Crumble Feta cheese in salads and over roasted vegetables, add it to
        your sandwiches, add it in tacos and other Mexican dishes. Feta can be also served alongside
        olives, peppers, olive oil, and fresh flatbread.</string>
    <string name="monterey_info">Monterey Jack is one of the few all-American cheeses. It’s a pale
        yellow semi-hard cheese made with cow’s milk. It has a mild and buttery flavor with a bit
        of tang, and it’s good for melting.
        It’s one of the best options for melting it in casseroles, including a classic like mac and
        cheese, for making sandwiches, cheese dips, and grilled cheese.</string>
    <string name="provolone_info">Provolone is an Italian semi-hard cheese. Its taste varies
        depending on its age; from sharp or spicy to sweet with a very mild taste. Some versions
        of provolone are smoked. You can use it to complete your casseroles, pizzas, sandwiches,
        and baked pasta dishes.</string>
    <string name="edam_info">Edam is a Dutch semi-hard cheese, traditionally sold in spheres with a
        pale-yellow interior and a coat of red paraffin wax. It has a very mild flavor, slightly
        salty or nutty, and almost odorless when compared to other cheeses. As the cheese ages,
        its flavor sharpens.
        Edam cheese goes well with chicken or potato dishes, in pasta, souffles, salads, fritters,
        soups, and sauces.</string>
    <string name="blue_cheese_info">Blue cheese is made with cow’s milk, sheep’s milk,
        or goat’s milk and has cultures of the mold Penicillium added. That leads to creating blue,
        blue-grey, blue-green, or blue-brown veins of mold in it. Also, Blue cheese has a distinct
        smell, that some people find unpleasant. It tastes like yeast, it’s a little spicy, and
        it’s creamy like butter. Blue cheese adds some class to a simple salad, roasted vegetables,
        or grilled fruit dessert. You can add pieces of blue cheese to top your veggie soup or
        puree.</string>
    <string name="gorgonzola_info">Gorgonzola is a type of blue cheese, but it’s special because
        of the small ‘blue’ stripes that actually has in it. It’s a mild, sweet, and milky cheese
        that is best served with a glass of red wine. You can also stir it into a risotto or slice
        it on your Quattro formaggi pizza.</string>
    <string name="roquefort_info">Roquefort is, together with Gorgonzola, one of the world’s best
        known blue cheeses. This French moldy cheese is like a moist, crumbly paste. It’s made
        from sheep’s milk and has a sharp, sweet, and nutty flavor that comes from the yeast.
        There are plenty of recipes that use Roquefort, thanks to its distinctive taste and its
        melting capacity. It’s best eaten as is, with crackers or toast, or with nuts and honey.</string>
    <string name="ricotta_info">Ricotta is an Italian whey cheese made from sheep’s milk.
        This smooth cheese with a creamy mild sweet and fresh taste and a thick texture is very
        versatile. Plus, it’s low in fat, which makes it a good choice for almost any diet.
        Thanks to its low salt content, Ricotta is perfect for both sweet and savory dishes.
        It’s actually perfect for everything from lasagna to pasta, from pies to cheesecakes.
        You can spread it on a bread slice and top it with veggies, sunny side up eggs, or fruit,
        and you can use it to make lots of dips.</string>
    <string name="cottage_cheese_info">Ricotta and cottage cheese are often compared and some people
        replace one with the other. But they aren’t all that similar. Cheesemakers separate milk or
        cream into curds and whey. Then, the curds are used to make cottage cheese and the whey is
        used to make ricotta. That’s the reason why both cheeses – Ricotta and cottage cheese – have
        different textures. But they’re both soft and mild in flavor.
        While Ricotta is described as sweet, cottage cheese is fresh, milky, and creamy, with a
        moderate saltiness to it. The texture of cottage cheese is chunky, from the curds.
        You can use it to top stuffed baked vegetables, like potatoes and pumpkins, in casseroles,
        pasta, to make a dip or a quick sweet snack (combining it with fruits and granola),
        in baked goods, or incorporated in smoothies.</string>
    <string name="mascarpone_info">Compared to Ricotta (which is smooth, but has a grainy texture),
        mascarpone has a very smooth texture with no lumps or granularities. Mascarpone is one of
        the most popular cheeses and is made from cream and citric or tartaric acid, which thickens
        the cream. It has a milky and slightly sweet taste and a buttery flavor which comes from its
        high butterfat content.
        Mascarpone is best known as an ingredient in the Italian dessert tiramisu. But you can also
        use it in pasta, mac and cheese, lasagna, or in fresh desserts. Or you can transform it
        into a dip by combining it with some olive oil, herbs and spices.</string>
    <string name="halloumi_info">Halloumi is a Cypriot semi-hard brined cheese made from a mixture
        of goat’s and sheep’s milk, and sometimes also cow’s milk. It’s the best cheese for grilling
        because it has a high melting point. Because it’s also a salty cheese, you should combine
        it with something that dims its strong taste.Just throw it on the grill, then serve it as a
        starter, drizzled with olive oil and some fresh mint leaves and a glass of wine. You can add
        it to salads, in omelets served with veggies, in couscous, seafood dishes, or pair it with
        fresh fruit such as watermelon and pomegranate.</string>


    <!-- Cheese production companies   -->
    <string name="cabot_title">Cabot Creamery</string>
    <string name="cowgirl_title">Cowgirl Creamery</string>
    <string name="grafton_title"> Grafton Village Cheese</string>
    <string name="kraft_title">Kraft Foods</string>
    <string name="vermont_title">Vermont Shepherd</string>

    <string name="cabot_info">The Cabot Creamery Cooperative is an American dairy agricultural
        marketing cooperative, which is owned by local dairy farmers in New England and the Agri-Mark Cooperative company.
        Originally started as Cabot Farmers Cooperative Creamery in 1919 by farmers in Cabot, Vermont,
        it was taken over by the Agri-Mark Cooperative in 1992. Although they are technically owned
        by Agri-Mark Co-op; local dairy farmers in New England own Cabot, also. </string>
    <string name="cowgirl_info">Cowgirl Creamery is a company located in Point Reyes Station,
        California, which manufactures artisan cheeses. Founded in 1994, the company manufactures
        its own cheeses and sells other imported and domestic cheese and fine artisan foods.
        Its own cheeses include Red Hawk and Mt. Tam (named after Mount Tamalpais). The company
        operates a storefront in the Ferry Building of San Francisco. Founders Peggy Smith and
        Sue Conley worked for years in the kitchens of the Bay Area, and Alice Waters\' Chez
        Panisse, where Peggy worked for many years, is among many Bay Area establishments to
        incorporate cheeses from Cowgirl Creamery into its menu.</string>
    <string name="grafton_info">The company is the successor to the 1892 Grafton Cooperative Cheese
        Company, which was founded to handle surplus local milk. The original company went out of
        business due to a fire. It was restored in the mid-1960s with help from the Windham Foundation,
        a nonprofit organization whose mission is to "preserve the vitality of Vermont\'srural communities".
        Grafton\'s cheddar is synthetic-hormone-free and made mostly from Jersey cow milk from
        Vermont family farms. The most common cheese offered by the Grafton Cheese is their block
        cheddar, made in 40 pound blocks and then cut to different sales sizes.
        In July 2008 the company celebrated the opening of a new production plant and retail store
        in Brattleboro. The shop is "a 2,500-square-foot classic barn-like structure encompassing
        a full-service artisanal cheese shop" offering "more than 70 types of cheeses, wine, Vermont
        microbrews, fresh bread, maple products and other gourmet food items and accompaniments.
        In 2014, the Grafton Spring Brook milk Cheese won the "Best USA Cheese trophy" at the 2014
        International Cheese Awards.</string>
    <string name="kraft_info">Kraft Foods Group, Inc. is an American grocery manufacturing and
        processing conglomerate headquartered in Chicago, Illinois, part of the Kraft Heinz
        Company.The company was restructured in 2012 as a spin off from Kraft Foods Inc.,
        which in turn was renamed Mondelez International. The new Kraft Foods Group was focused
        mainly on grocery products for the North American market while Mondelez is focused on
        international confectionery and snack brands. Until the merger with Heinz, Kraft Foods
        Group was an independent public company listed on the NASDAQ stock exchange.
        On July 2, 2015, Kraft completed its merger with Heinz, arranged by Heinz owners Berkshire
        Hathaway and 3G Capital, creating the fifth-largest food and beverage company in the
        world, Kraft Heinz Company.</string>
    <string name="vermont_info">Since 1993, Vermont Shepherd has made , their award-winning
        flagship cheese. Made in the springtime, when the sheep have been grazing on pastures and
        fields, Verano is a sheep’s milk cheese that’s available from August to April.
        Vermont Shepherd is the creation of the Major and Ielpi family, who own and run one Vermont’s
        oldest sheep farms, also called Vermont Shepherd (formerly Major Farm). Having bought the farm
        from his parents, David Major was among the first small-scale cheesemakers in the United States
        to begin producing sheep\'s milk cheese in the 1990s.</string>
    <string name="logo_image">Logo</string>


</resources>
